ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Born Digital Material /4283/001 (d)
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Born Digital Material
1999- 2005
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Fleron, Lou Jean
/4283/001 (d)
0.72 cubic feet
0.7 linear ft.
Digital.
9267732
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
M. Clark, January 08, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 28, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4283: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Files /4283 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Audio-Visual Materials /4283 MB: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Memorabilia /4283 P: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Photographs /4283/001: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Files /4283/001 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Audio-Visual Materials /4283/001 MB: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Memorabilia /4283/001 PUBS: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Publications /4283/002: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Files /4283/002 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Audio-Visual Materials /4283/002 P: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Photographs
Fleron, Lou Jean; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Extension and Public Service Division; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
9267732
- CDA Usage Intensity (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Prof. L. Turner's - WEM presentation 5/25/2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Prof. L. Turner's -- WEM Presentation 5/25/2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Lowell Turner -- WEM Presentation 5/25/2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Champions at Work - *Arvin Jones + Jeff Paycheck - 1/16/200 *Barb Bauch - 1/7/00 *Jack Barrett + Mike Scott - 12/7/99 *Bob Klinko: Richard Lipsitz - 12/6/99 *Cynthia Banks + Bill Pienta - 12/14/99 [Microsoft Word 2000], 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Champions at Work Interviews -- *Mark Jones - 11/13/99 *Tom Wisniewski - 11/18/99 *Kevin Clark - 11/23/99 *Joe Goodell - 12/01/99 *Ken Owens - 12/9/99 [Microsoft Word 2000], 1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Champions At Work -- *Ron Lucas *William McGee * Tom Fentner *George Koller *Mark, Kirsh + Dan Boody *Warren Bartel *Vern Wetmoe *Charles Humphrey *Deborah Hayes *Jack Williams *Kevin Donovan *Tony Strusa (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Champions at Work - *Richard Lipsitz - 2/16/00 *Niagara County Group - 2/22/00 *Jim Voye - 2/24/00 *Martin Oscadal - 2/10/00, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- TOPS pics (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Kumiega Pictures 6-15-2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Jack Koebler Moog (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Final Extension Annual Report form (M-word) 4.0 Mac, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Niagara Mohawk IBEW Present (Hamilton + Buffalo 3/23-3/26/99) 1) Dialogue Process Overheads-Final-Bernie Flaherty 2) NiagMohawk Book 1+2-Final-Sid Finkel 3) Taking Charge in a Rapidly Changing World-Final-Bernie Flaherty (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Vision 2001 Logo (Box 1, Folder 14)
- NIMO-IBEW-Cornell -- March 23-24 + 25-26/99 -- Karlin Jessen-Yankee Group.ppt, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- NIMO - IBEW - CORNELL -- 2 Programs 3/23 + 3/24/99 And 3/25 + 3/26/99 -- Hamilton + Buffalo, NY *Dialogue Process Overheads - FINAL.ppt *Niag Mohawk Book 1 + 2 - FINAL.ppt *NIMO MASTER SLIDES.ppt (Box 1, Folder 16)
- NIMO - IBEW - CORNELL -- 2 Programs 3/23 + 3/24/99 And 3/25 + 3/26/99 Hamilton + Buffalo, NY [Taking Charge in a Rapidly Changing World-FINAL.ppt], 1999 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Erie County Community Coalition, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Unlabeled (Box 1, Folder 19)
- NiMo Folder (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Cornell (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Champions - *7087.tif *7091.tif *City Straight.tif *Champions Ch 12 + Dir Images II *Chautaqua.tif *Cornell Logo 2 color.eps *Darwin House.tif *Erie County Map Flattened.tif *Power plant.tif (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Scope and Contents
  MAC100
- Graph 2.eps *Graph 3.eps [will not open] (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Champions - *1315.tif *1317.tif *14008.tif *14036.tif *14255.tif *7003.tif *Man with map.tif *Metro B&W.tif (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Champions - *14258.tif *5322.tif *7018.tif *7025.tif *7047.tif *7094.tif *Kleinhans.tif, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- WEM Delegate Visit to American 5/23-5/26/00, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Video developed by: State University of NYS@Buffalo - Institute for Local Governance & Regional Growth (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Champions - Ch 1-2 Images II / *Airport.tif *City Hall.tif - Champions Ch 3-4 images / *1201.tif *Darwin House.tif *Marina w/Orange sky.tif, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Champions - *Ch 3-4 Charts and Graphs *~Images Champions 1,2,3, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Champions - *41.tif *BPO.tif *gm.tif, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Champions - *1158.tif *1179.tif *1317.tif *14306.tif *15109.tif *Waterfront.tif, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Champions - *#41 *1394 b&w.tif *binder Quebecor.tif *BPOnew.tif *ChildrensHosp.tif *chslogo.tif *DeaconessCtr.tif *DeGraffHosp.tif *GM Pwrtr.tif * gm.plant.tif *Grain Ele.tif *Kaleida.2c.2.eps *MFSurbHosp.tif *Millardgts.tif *Moogca, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Champions - *#85 *1317.tif *14035.tif *14148.tif *14255.tif *7001.tif *7003.tif *Family @ Waterfront.tif, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Champions - *1156.tif *1180.tif *1367.tif *14181.tif *7015.tif *casting1.tif *casting2.tif *Chautaqua Inst *Power plant.tif *stonebuffalo.tif, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Labor Database - volume 6/January 2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Loop demo of disk for 5/25/00 WEM Delegate Visit Roycroft Inn. Video developed by: State University of NY@Buffalo Institute for Local Governance & Regional Growth, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 1)